Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the Red Velvet Cake
Blizzard. And yes, it passes the
Blizzard test.
>> No shot. Let me show you how to make it.
We're starting off with 400 g of
fat-free high protein milk, followed by
some vanilla bean paste, cream cheese,
sweetener, salt, zantham gum. Then we'll
just blend that up with an immersion
blender and throw it in the freezer.
Then you can grab your favorite red
velvet cake. I'm using this Prime Bites
protein brownie, which is basically just
a slice of red velvet cake, but packed
with protein. We're just going to chop
that up into bite-sized pieces and throw
it in the freezer alongside that ice
cream. These are both going to stay in
there for at least 16 hours. The reason
we're freezing the brownie is so it can
firm up so it doesn't get obliterated by
the mixing setting. Alternatively, you
can just throw all these pieces on top
and mix them in by hand, which is what I
do sometimes. So, after that first spin,
you're going to take it out, scrape down
all the sides with a butter knife, and
then hollow out a hole in the middle for
your brownie pieces. We're going to fill
that hole with the brownie pieces.
Really shove them down there.